[{"answer": "That is absolutely the case, Piers.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "How can we read into this from the information today?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "You know, I really don't know how they couldn't have a clue that they were there, but we know that when victims -- we work at Bellefaire with victims of sexual trafficking and abuse and neglect, and when they are under the control of someone that is so aggressive and abusing them physically and sexually, they develop a learned helplessness, and a learned helplessness.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "What is your explanation if you like for how this could have happen and how nobody could have even had a clue that they were there?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes, they do a great deal of manipulating and they really mess with -- they really -- with their minds -- they make them very un-empowered and they put a great deal of fear over them, whether they are going to hurt themselves or hurt their family members or hurt somebody else.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "And is this the kind of thing that the sex traffickers in your experience do to these young women to ensure they stay in captivity?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I was very just -- I didn't know how I felt.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "What is your reaction to this discovery?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I mean I knew him for 22 years since I was 5 years old.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What kind of man is he?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, Mr. Morgan to be honest, I thought the house is vacant the last couple of years.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Did you have any concerns over the last ten years that something may not be entirely right about this man's house?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "A lot of people are scratching their heads.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "What is your make of that?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, I mean there was no question that she had done it.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "What is your reaction to the verdict today?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I agree with that part.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Why do you say that?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, yes.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "What is your reaction to what happened?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "You know, I have forgiven her a long time ago.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "And, Elisha, do you think that she should get the death penalty?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, here's what you've got to look at.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What do you think of her mental state?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, based on what the jury saw and heard, this is what they have done.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Gus, what is your reaction to what Vinnie just said?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "I've seen the photos and I've listened to you.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Did you see the photographs?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Yes, she could have shot him in his sleep.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Did you see the photos after what she did?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well, she wants it.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Should she get, Jodi Arias, the death penalty that she now says that she wants?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Vinnie Politan and Gus Searcy --", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "So, why won't the eight men and four women of Maricopa County give her what she wants?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Let me see your driver's license, please.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Excuse me?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "First off, your plate is improperly displayed.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What's wrong?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Because he's a sociopath.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What was your take of it?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Who are we looking for here?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Well, there's another little girl, you know, missing in that six blocks from Gina DeJesus.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "What do you do with stuff like this?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I am the biggest supporter of law enforcement.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "You put it all together, and you've got a bit of a mess by the Cleveland police, to put it mildly, haven't you?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Well, let me say this too, Piers.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "But, when you put together also all of the appalling errors in the Cleveland strangler investigation, none of this looks good for Cleveland police generally, does it?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I don't know, Piers.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Do you believe from everything you have seen that she may be in some way linked to Ariel Castro too?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I can just say that in the few seconds that I have seen her that she is very quiet, but very happy and very grateful to be home with her friends and family.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "How is Gina today, would you say?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I really have no comment personally for that question, I'm sorry.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "How would you describe that?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "The family is totally, totally, totally overwhelmed and grateful and happy.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "They must be absolutely overjoyed, aren't they, to have their girl back?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Well, we won't know until more evidence is uncovered and as to how effective he was in keeping what he was doing secret.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Do you believe they drop the ball?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with Alan that we have to appear as wait for all of the facts to be known before we reach conclusions.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Do you think that the police really have made serious errors here to as some belief?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "It is incredibly heinous.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What do you think of what we're learning?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Well, that sometimes is a tactic.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Well, I think it is for the jury to decide, and I don't want to invade the problems of the jury.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Do you think that she deserves it for the crime that she is now being convicted of?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "AIRSTEIN: I cannot understand for a minute why we are so obsessed with this case.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Is there something particularly fascinating about these two women that drives this kind of extraordinary interest, really, because there are many cases that are not dissimilar to this?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Is it television --", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I don't think it aids at all.", "docId": "130508pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Do you think that it aids the legal processes or perhaps gets in the way in and is a hindrance?", "qSentId": 597}]